# Shaker Kattoula

Oceanside, CA | smkattoula@gmail.com | Linkedin.com/in/shakerkattoula | Portfolio: shakerkattoula.com

### **SUMMARY**

Software Developer from San Diego with a strong passion for problem-solving and engineering creative solutions using code. Reflective communicator and collaborative team member. Backed with over 5+ years of professional customer service and operations management.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

April 2020 – June 2020

## Full Stack Software Developer Intern (Remote), Victorise, Carlsbad, CA

- Used the MERN stack to connect front-end/backend and improve existing web application UI features
- Created UX analysis bug reports for both web and mobile applications
- Improved functionality of UI features on mobile application using React Native
- Communicated effectively with the project manager on a daily basis to ensure timely completion of tasks and quality assurance
- Utilized weekly sprint planning via Agile methodology

May 2016 - March 2020

Store Operations Manager, Minute Ship Liquor and Deli, Solana Beach, CA

- Operated the store very efficiently with zero supervision while ensuring that only the highest standards were met
- Managed up to 5 different employees and was responsible for coordinating each person's schedule
- Maintained appropriate levels of inventory throughout the business and ensured proper pricing
- Upheld a professional work attitude at all times even while handling the most difficult customers

### **VOLUNTEER WORK**

April 2020 – July 2020

Teacher's Assistant, LEARN Academy, San Diego, CA

### **SKILLS**

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, NodeJS/Express, MongoDB, jQuery, Bootstrap, Mongoose, Git Flow, GitHub, Testing(jest/enzyme), RESTful API's(JSON), CRUD functionality, State Management, User Authentication

### **EDUCATION**

August 2015 - May 2019

California State University of San Marcos - Bachelor's Degree, Psychology

January 2020 - April 2020

LEARN Academy - Full Stack Web Development